A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Snapshot Files, RG 4 FA1128C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Houses (200), 1930-1994; 3
  - 200,024 Woodstock, 1971 August (Box 4)
    French family reunion at Billings Farm.
  - 200,025 Woodstock, 1975 (Box 4)
    French family picnic.
  - 200,026 Woodstock - Lakota Fishing Club, 1975 August (Box 4)
  - 200,027 Woodstock, 1975 August (Box 4)
    Woodstock views.
  - 200,028 Woodstock and other views, 1975 October (Box 4)
    John French; wildlife in Wyoming
  - 200,029 Woodstock garden, 1976 September (Box 4)
  - 200,030 Woodstock, circa 1977 (Box 4)
    Lady Bird Johnson, MFR, LSR, dogs, etc.
  - 200,031 Trees, 1978 November (Box 4)
  - 200,032 Woodstock, 1979 July (Box 4)
    Band outside Woodstock Inn; MFR and McDills
  - 200,033 Two unidentified men, 1979 August (Box 4)
  - 200,034 Woodstock and Catskills, NY, 1979 November; 1986 (Box 4)
    Horses pulling log; Dai Bosatsu Zendo.
  - 200,035 Woodstock and New York, circa 1980 (Box 4)
    Asian and other art; snow on sculpture. Includes image of Sirkha Ahlskog, NAR's cook
  - 200,036 Woodstock buildings, 1981 January (Box 4)
    Views of vacant office; buildings.
  - 200,037 Woodstock, 1981 July (Box 4)
    Pollution control work; museum and town.
  - 200,038 Echo Acre, Woodstock, circa 1981 (Box 4)
    View of Echo Acres house and river.
  - 200,039 Woodstock, 1981 July (Box 4)
    Woodstock Mansion; MFR.
  - 200,040 Vermont (Woodstock and Calvin Coolidge Homestead) and Billings Monument Unveiling, Montana, 1982 July (Box 4)
  - 200,040a Miscellaneous, 1946; 1962-1963; 1980s (Box 4)
    Jenny Lake, Jackson Hole (photo by H. J. Coolidge), 1946 July; LSR and MFR on resort golf course (National Geographic photo, B. A. Stewart), 1962 January; 4 unidentified slides, 1963. Envelope includes transparency of inscribed portrait of NAR and LSR.
  - 200,041 Calvin Coolidge Homestead, Plymouth, VT, 1982 (Box 4)
    LSR visit.
  - 200,042 Woodstock - French Family Picnic, circa 1982 (Box 4)
  - 200,043 Riding Stable, South Woodstock, circa 1982 (Box 4)
  - 200,044 Woodstock, 1982 July (Box 4)
    River, gardens, horse and carriage at Mansion.
  - 200,045 Vermont, 1982 August (Box 4)
  - 200,046 Vermont, 1982 September (Box 4)
    Views, Woodstock and Coolidge Homestead, Incudes men at dinner table in plaid jackets.
  - 200,047 Woodstock, 1979 October (Box 4)
    Views and Billings Farm and Museum.
  - 200,048 Woodstock, 1983 (Box 4)
    Horse and foal, town views, LSR.
  - 200,049 Woodstock, 1983 March (Box 4)
  - 200,050 Woodstock, 1983 March (Box 4)
    LSR, MFR, horsedrawn wagon, grandchildren.
  - 200,050.1 Billings Farm Museum, 1983 May (Box 4)
  - 200,050.2 Billings Farm and Museum, 1983 July (Box 4)
    Includes MFR, Happy Rockefeller visit to Larry R. in Catskills
  - 200,050.3 Billings Farm and Museum, 1983 July (Box 4)
  - 200,050.4 French Family Party; Wyoming; 834 Fifth Ave, early 1950s; 1983 (Box 4)
    Early photos of MFR and children riding, JY Ranch; Lincoln School dinner at 834 Fifth Ave
  - 200,051 Woodstock Mansion, 1983 October (Box 4)
    Envelope also marked Rockwood Hall; Holly Hill?
  - 200,052 Woodstock, 1983 November (Box 4)
    Parade, flowers.
  - 200,052.2 Woodstock Mansion Renovations, 1956 (Box 4)
  - 200,053 Woodstock, 1984 May (Box 5)
    Billings Farm and Museum.
  - 200,054 Woodstock, 1984 July (Box 5)
    One image- child in raccoon hat.
  - 200,055 Woodstock, 1984 August (Box 5)
    LSR and MFR at Woodstock mansion; pool.
  - 200,056 Woodstock, 1984 August (Box 5)
    Views. Prints and slides.
  - 200,057 Woodstock, 1984 October (Box 5)
    LSR and MFR at Billings Farm, Belvedere, dogs.
  - 200,058 Woodstock, circa 1984 (Box 5)
    LSR and MFR at ribbon-cutting (for Billings Farm visitor center or Woodstock Inn fitness center). Includes misfiled photo of LSR at formal event, includes Mamdouha Bobst
  - 200,059 Woodstock, Undated (Box 5)
    MFR; artwork; images of Bob Barton and Scott Hastings; children in pool.
  - 200,060 Woodstock, Undated (Box 5)
    Billings Museum displays.
  - 200,061 Wyoming and Woodstock, 1980s (Box 5)
    Woodstock gardens; French family reunion; LSR and MFR anniversary at JY Ranch; family and grandchildren.
  - 200,062 Woodstock Inn, Undated (Box 5)
    Miscellaneous snapshots.
  - 200,063 Woodstock, Undated (Box 5)
    Woodstock winter views; LSR at Billings Farm
  - 200,064 Woodstock - Echo Acre, Undated (Box 5)
    Color negatives.
  - 200,065 Woodstock and Wyoming, 1980s (Box 5)
  - 200,065.1 Woodstock, 1988; undated (Box 5)
    Woodstock mansion, art, luncheon on porch; Billings Farm, draft horses, bicycles.
  - 200,065.2 Woodstock, 1989 (Box 5)
    Woodstock views; Woodstock Inn.
  - 200,065.3 Woodstock, Undated (Box 5)
    Woodstock views and mansion.
  - 200,066 Wyoming, circa 1934 (Box 5)
    LSR and MFR on horseback and at Jackson Lake.
  - 200,067 Wyoming, 1930s - late 1940s (Box 5)
    LSR by Phelps Lake; children
  - 200,068 Wyoming, circa 1940s (Box 5)
    LSR, MFR, and children. Horseback riding; cookouts. Duplicates of images in other envelopes.
  - 200,069 Wyoming, 1940s-1950s (Box 5)
    Views, rodeo, cookouts, horseback riding.
  - 200,070 Wyoming, late 1940s - 1950s (Box 5)
    Children at JY, views.
  - 200,071 Wyoming, 1950s (Box 5)
    LSR, MFR, children, views, fishing, riding.
  - 200,072 Wyoming, 1950s (Box 5)
    JY Ranch views, children, activities.
  - 200,073 Wyoming, 1940s (Box 5)
    JY Ranch views, MFR, Phelps Lake.
  - 200,074 Wyoming, 1930s (Box 5)
    JY Ranch and MFR.
  - 200,075 Wyoming, 1930s (Box 5)
    Unidentified men and women on western pack trip. Black and white prints.
  - 200,076 Wyoming, 1934-1955 (Box 5)
    LSR and MFR hunting; 1955 raft trip; group picnic; rodeo. LSR and MFR informal portraits.
  - 200,077 Wyoming, early 1950s (Box 5)
    JY views, Phelps Lake, LSR and Sheffield children, rodeo, bear.
  - 200,078 Wyoming, circa 1970s (Box 5)
    JY views, family and friends.
  - 200,079 Wyoming (Box 5)
  - 200,080 Wyoming, 1970s-1980s (Box 5)
    Artwork, MFR, museum, unidentified building; Gary Everhardt with Josephine and Harold Fabian, 1970s.
  - 200,081 Wyoming, circa 1955 (Box 5)
    Jackson Lake Lodge cottages; Chorley and others; scenic views of GTNP, MFR and girls at Yellowstone.
  - 200,082 Wyoming, 1975 (Box 5)
    Friends of Hospital sculpture award; group picnic at JY Ranch; views.
  - 200,083 Wyoming, 1980s (Box 5)
    LSR, Mrs. Bobst, group at JY Ranch.
  - 200,084 Wyoming, 1980s (Box 5)
    Laura and Dick Chasin, MFR, DR and Peggy R., and others at JY Ranch.
  - 200,085 Wyoming (Box 5)
    Furniture store.
  - 200,085 Wyoming, 1950 October (Box 5)
    LSR family swimming, picnicking; buffalo.
  - 200,085.1 Wyoming, circa 1980s (Box 5)
  - 200,086 Unidentified man in tropical garden, 1954 April 27 (Box 5)
  - 200,087 Wyoming, 1954 October 29 (Box 5)
    MFR informal portraits; MFR and LSR with Larry; Red Mathews with Marion; Jackson Lake and Lunch Tree Hill plaque. Also includes MFR on sailboat.
  - 200,088 Wyoming, 1954 November 2 (Box 5)
    JDR Jr. Plaque on Lunch Tree Hill.
  - 200,089 Wyoming, 1956 October 20 (Box 6)
    JY and Jackson Lake views. Images faded; see enlargements in 200,092.
  - 200,090 Aspen, Colorado, 1957 (Box 6)
    LSR family on ski lift (summertime)
  - 200,091 Wyoming, 1957 (Box 6)
    Faded images. Boating and canoeing on Phelps Lake; Larry and friend; MFR.
  - 200,092 Wyoming, 1957 February 7 (Box 6)
    JY views. Enlargeent of images in 200,089.
  - 200,093 Wyoming, 1958 February (Box 6)
    Red Mathews, man shaving.
  - 200,094 Wyoming, 1958 October 13 (Box 6)
    Board meeting at GTNP, LSR and Larry chopping and loading wood, bulldozer, Jackson Lake views.
  - 200,095 Wyoming, 1958 October 20 (Box 6)
    Larry R. and friend by woodpile.
  - 200,096 Wyoming, 1959 September (Box 6)
    LSR family on horseback (group photos); Phelps Lake views; airplane.
  - 200,096.1 Wyoming, 1959 September (Box 6)
    LSR family, JY building, Phelps Lake views.
  - 200,096.2 Wyoming, 1959 September (Box 6)
    Teton views, Phelps Lake, LSR family.
  - 200,097 Unidentified, 1960 August (Box 6)
    LSR standing by cactus.
  - 200,098 Wyoming, 1961 July (Box 6)
    JY Ranch, LSR with Horace Albright, Harold Fabian, and others.
  - 200,099 Wyoming, 1962 February (Box 6)
    Unidentified mountain lodge and pool.
  - 200,100 Wyoming, 1964 August (Box 6)
    LSR, Larry R., and others at JY Ranch.
  - 200,101 Wyoming, 1966 September (Box 6)
    Meeting at JY Ranch. LSR, Albright?, and others.
  - 200,102 Wyoming, 1968 August (Box 6)
    JY Ranch building.
  - 200,102.1 Wyoming, 1968 October (Box 6)
    LSR, meeting at JY Ranch, visitors.
  - 200,102.2 Wyoming, 1969 September (Box 6)
    JY Ranch - LSR, board meeting, wildlife
  - 200,103 Wyoming, 1970 October (Box 6)
    Flowers in landscape.
  - 200,104 Wyoming, 1971 February (Box 6)
    Horses crossing String Lake, near Jenny Lake Lodge.
  - 200,105 Wyoming, 1971-1973 (Box 6)
    Flowers, family, meeting at JY.
  - 200,105.9 Wyoming, 1974 September (Box 6)
    Lady Bird Johnson and others at JY, raft trip.
  - 200,106 Wyoming, 1975 August (Box 6)
    JY Ranch pool.
  - 200,107 Wyoming, 1975 September (Box 6)
    Wildflowers and animals.
  - 200,108 Wyoming, 1975 September (Box 6)
    JY Ranch, moose, wildflowers, visitors.
  - 200,109 Wyoming, 1976 August (Box 6)
    Moose, lake view.
  - 200,110 Wyoming, 1976 September (Box 6)
    Meeting at JY Ranch - Lady Bird Johnson, Nash Castro, and others
  - 200,111 Wyoming, 1977 September (Box 6)
    Moose; negatives of LSR at JY Ranch.
  - 200,111.1 Wyoming, 1977 October (Box 6)
    JY Ranch views, LSR and MFR, Jackson Lake Lodge.
  - 200,112 Wyoming, 1978 August (Box 6)
    LSR, MFR, unidentified visitors, at JY Ranch
  - 200,012.1 Wyoming, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
    Mamdouha Bobst at JY Ranch. Photos taken from envelopes 200,113 - 200,115 and 200,120 - 200,121.
  - 200,013 Wyoming, 1978 September (Box 6)
    Teton views; LSR and MFR with unidentified visitors at JY Ranch; Remington sculptures.
  - 200,114 Wyoming, 1978 September (Box 6)
  - 200,115 Wyoming, 1978 October (Box 6)
    LSR and MFR on raft; two images of unidentified conservation group meeting, including Henry Diamond
  - 200,116 Wyoming, circa 1979 (Box 6)
    LSR, MFR, and other unidentified people at building site in Wyoming.
  - 200,117 Wyoming, 1979 June (Box 6)
    Lake and boathouse views.
  - 200,118 Wyoming, 1979 July (Box 6)
  - 200,119 Wyoming, 1979 August (Box 6)
    Family, visitors, and JY Ranch views.
  - 200, 120 Wyoming, 1979 September (Box 6)
    Golf course; views.
  - 200,121 Wyoming, 1979 July (Box 6)
    Josephine Fabian, Leonard Firestone, Mamdouha Bobst, LSR and MFR, views.
  - 200,121.1 Wyoming, 1979 September (Box 6)
    LSR children and grandchildren.
  - 200,122 Wyoming, 1980s (Box 7)
    Guest house.
  - 200,123 Wyoming, circa 1980s (Box 7)
    Family and guests; Native American baskets and artwork.
  - 200,124 Wyoming, circa 1980s (Box 7)
    Winter views, horses; Native American baskets and artifacts.
  - 200,125 Wyoming, circa 1980 (Box 7)
    JY views, flowers, wildlife; LSR on horseback.
  - 200,126 Wyoming, circa 1980s (Box 7)
    Valley Ranch house construction; JY views, family.
  - 200,127 Wyoming, 1980 September (Box 7)
    LSR with camera; JY and lake views.
  - 200,128 Wyoming, 1980s (Box 7)
    Views; LSR with Leonard Firestone; Mrs. Bobst; children and grandchildren.
  - 200,128.1 Wyoming, 1981 September (Box 7)
    Valley Ranch house construction; Colter Bay Indian Art Museum.
  - 200,129 Wyoming, 1981 (Box 7)
    Furniture for Valley Ranch house; Mrs. Bobst.
  - 200,130 Wyoming, circa 1981 (Box 7)
    Valley Ranch construction.
  - 200,131 Wyoming, circa 1981 (Box 7)
  - 200,131.1 Wyoming, 1981 August (Box 7)
    Valley Ranch construction, views, golf course, LSR.
  - 200,131.2 Wyoming, 1981 August (Box 7)
    Moose, views, Jackson Hole airport.
  - 200,132 Wyoming, 1982 (Box 7)
    Wildflowers. Includes disk negative.
  - 200,133 Wyoming, circa 1982 (Box 7)
    JY Ranch views, Phelps Lake; Indian baskets; MFR with unidentified guest.
  - 200,134 Wyoming, 1982 April (Box 7)
    LBJ Ranch; Valley Ranch?; Roundup gift shop; Indian blankets.
  - 200,135 Wyoming, 1982 (Box 7)
    JY Ranch views; LSR at Valley Ranch.
  - 200,136 Wyoming, 1982 July (Box 7)
    Valley Ranch
  - 200,137 Wyoming, 1982 July (Box 7)
    Valley Ranch; LSR and MFR, and others. Unidentified group photo with park ranger.
  - 200,138 Wyoming, 1982 July (Box 7)
  - 200,139 Wyoming, 1982 July (Box 7)
    Dog, Jackson clubhouse, Ruth Haupert.
  - 200,140 Wyoming, 1982 July (Box 7)
    Chapel of the Transfiguration (LSR, MFR, Lucy).
  - 200,141 Wyoming, 1982 July (Box 7)
    Valley Ranch, Indian baskets and pottery; Lucy R.
  - 200,142 Wyoming, 1982 August (Box 7)
    JY Ranch views, family; one image from Woodstock, VT.
  - 200,143 Wyoming, 1982 August (Box 7)
    Laura at JY Ranch; unidentified construction.
  - 200,144 Wyoming, 1982 September (Box 7)
    Valley Ranch house, Bill and Polly Billings.
  - 200,145 Wyoming, 1982 September (Box 7)
    JY Ranch winter views; JY staff.
  - 200,146 Wyoming, 1982 September (Box 7)
    JY Ranch and Valley Ranch; golf course; views.
  - 200,147 Wyoming, 1982 August (Box 8)
    Construction of Beaver Creek, WY, houses?
  - 200,148 Wyoming, 1982 August (Box 8)
    Vallley Ranch artwork; LSR with Leonard Firestone.
  - 200,149 Wyoming, circa 1983 (Box 8)
    LSR family.
  - 200,150 Wyoming, circa 1983 (Box 8)
    Appeal to the Great Spirit sculpture; JY and Valley Ranch views; MFR with Wes Frye and Carlisle Humelsine.
  - 200,151 Wyoming, 1983 (Box 8)
    Valley Ranch house construction photos.
  - 200,151.1 Wyoming, 1983 (Box 8)
    Valley Ranch rugs and artwork.
  - 200,151.2 Wyoming, 1983 circa August (Box 8)
    Marion Weber with wool; artwork; grandchildren.
  - 200,151.3 Wyoming, 1983 circa August (Box 8)
    JY and Valley Ranch views; MFR; unidentified guests.
  - 200,151.4 Wyoming, 1983 circa August (Box 8)
    JY Ranch - horses, family.
  - 200,151.5 Wyoming, 1983 (Box 8)
    JY and Valley Ranch scenic views.
  - 200,152 Wyoming, 1963; circa 1984 (Box 8)
    LSR and Larry by woodpile; MFR on horseback and painting; DR ad Peggy R., LSR family.
  - 200,153 Wyoming, 1984 (Box 8)
    Marion spinning yarn. MFR.
  - 200,154 Wyoming, 1984 August (Box 8)
    Meeting at JY Ranch - includes LSR, Wes Frye, Franklin Parker, Nash Castro, and others; LSR with Lady Bird Johnson.
  - 200,155 Wyoming, 1984 August 15 (Box 8)
    LSR and MFR fiftieth wedding anniversary, JY Ranch. Black and white prints.
  - 200,156 Wyoming and Woodstock, 1984 August 25 (Box 8)
    Valley Ranch and Wyoming views and gardens; Woodstock gardens.
  - 200,157 Wyoming, 1984 September (Box 8)
    Wyoming visits - MFR and Mamdouha Bobst, Ruth Haupert, friends (Florence and Gerald van der Kemp?)?
  - 200,158 Wyoming, 1984 November (Box 8)
    MFR, DR, Peggy R. on horseback; Laura and Dick Chasin; family. Some duplicates of images in 200,152.
  - 200,159 Wyoming, 1984 November (Box 8)
    Valley Ranch artwork, pools, wildflowers. Includes MFR.
  - 200,160 Wyoming, 1985 May; 1988 (Box 8)
    JY Ranch, LSR, Larry R., Frank Borman, John Sargeant of Doubleday, Betty Sargeant. Pets; LSR family at Kent House and Woodstock, 1988.
  - 200,161 834 Fifth Ave, 1985 August (Box 8)
    Views from 834 Fifth Ave; construction of Central Park zoo?
  - 200,162 Pocantico, circa 1985 (Box 8)
    MFR, Kent House grounds and sculpture.
  - 200,163 Pocantico, 1985 July (Box 8)
    LSR and MFR at Kykuit; DR and Peggy R. outside Hudson Pines; Paul Maze visit.
  - 200,164 Wyoming and Pocantico, 1985 July (Box 8)
    Paul Maze visit to JY Ranch.
  - 200,165 Woodstock and Pocantico, 1985 July (Box 8)
    Paul Maze visit to Woodstock and Kent House.
  - 200,166 Woodstock, 1985 July (Box 8)
    MFR, Woodstock and Billings Farm.
  - 200,166a Woodstock, 1988 February (Box 8)
    Woodstock winter views, MFR, Marion.
  - 200,167 Woodstock, 1985 July (Box 8)
    French family reunion, Woodstock. MFR, Laura.
  - 200,168 Woodstock, 1985 July (Box 8)
    LSR, MFR, Billings Farm Museum, grandchildren, French family.
  - 200,169 Wyoming, 1985 July (Box 9)
    MFR, Mazes, Lynch house?, construction site.
  - 200,169a Woodstock, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
    Woodstock carriage ride, Billings Farm, MFR, French family, Peggy R.? feeding cattle.
  - 200,169.1 Wyoming, 1985 July (Box 9)
    LSR with Leonard Firestone and others at JY.
  - 200,170 Wyoming, 1985 July (Box 9)
    Paul Maze visit to JY Ranch, LSR, MFR.
  - 200,171 Wyoming, 1985 July (Box 9)
    JY Ranch - damage from fallen tree.
  - 200,172 Wyoming, 1985 August (Box 9)
    JY Ranch scenic views - includes MFR.
  - 200,173 Wyoming, 1985 August (Box 9)
    LSR and MFR on raft trip. Mr. and Mrs. Zubin Mehta visit, and others.
  - 200,174 Wyoming, 1985 August (Box 9)
    LSR and MFR in Wyoming; unidentified guests.
  - 200,175 Wyoming, 1985 September (Box 9)
    JY Ranch - LSR, MFR, Larry R, DR and Peggy, grandchildren, others.
  - 200,175.1 Wyoming, 1986 September (Box 9)
    LSR, MFR, Wendy R., grandchildren at JY Ranch.
  - 200,175.2 Wyoming, 1986 September (Box 9)
    MFR, Marion, grandchildren at JY Ranch.
  - 200,175.3 Wyoming, 1986 September (Box 9)
    LSR and MFR at JY Ranch; polaroid of MFR, Lady Bird Johnson, Nash Castro, and others in Wyoming; Larry R. in Catskills.
  - 200,176 Woodstock, 1986 February (Box 9)
    Fitness Center construction, Woodstock Resort; LSR, MFR; Woodstock views; painted portraits of children.
  - 200,177 Woodstock, 1986 Summer (Box 9)
    Billings Farm, French family, MFR with Bonsai (Kent House?)
  - 200,178 Woodstock, 1986 July (Box 9)
    Photos marked to show site of proposed commercial building on LSR land.
  - 200,179 Wyoming, 1986 Summer (Box 9)
    Wyoming views and wildlife.
  - 200,180 Wyoming, 1986 (Box 9)
    Firestone house, Jackson Hole; views; unidentified party.
  - 200,181 Caribbean, 1986-1987 Winter (Box 9)
    Carambola Resort (Fountain Valley), St. Croix; Vermont?
  - 200,182 Woodstock, 1987 (Box 9)
    Woodstock, Billings Farm, French family, MFR and grandchildren.
  - 200,183 Wyoming, 1987 Summer (Box 9)
    JY Ranch, visitors, family and grandchildren.
  - 200,184 Wyoming, 1987 August - September (Box 9)
    JY Ranch visits- Marian Albright Schenck with LSR and Lady Bird Johnson; Frank and Susan Borman (negatives only); Paul and Joan Marks. Scenic views from Valley Ranch and JY Ranch, Phelps Lake; portraits of LSR and MFR in Wyoming landscape; 1987 Christmas card of Valley Ranch.
  - 200,185 Woodstock, circa 1988 (Box 9)
    LSR, MFR, and unidentified friends at Woodstock.
  - 200,185.1 Rockefeller Center, 1988 January (Box 9)
    Man standing by JDR Jr. "I Believe" plaque; skater.
  - 200,186 Wyoming, circa 1989 (Box 9)
    JY Ranch views, family, grandchildren; paintings in Jackson Lake Lodge.
- Miscellaneous (300), 1930-1989; 4
  - 300,000 Long Island, 1957 October 10 (Box 10)
    Two prints- includes Larry R. on boat approaching shore.
  - 300,001 Unidentified water views, 1954 May (Box 10)
    Deteriorated color snapshots.
  - 300,002 JY views, 1956 October (Box 10)
    Two prints- Includes MFR sitting by tree at Phelps Lake.
  - 300,003 Unidentified building, 1957 February (Box 10)
  - 300,004 Maine, 1957 (Box 10)
    Boat in harbor.
  - 300,005 Empty envelope, 1958 March 9 (Box 10)
  - 300,006 MFR in western dress, 1958 October (Box 10)
    Unidentified occasion; with others.
  - 300,007 Helicopter (at Dorado Beach?), 1960 July (Box 10)
    Roosevelt Roads, Navy. One image (3 copies).
  - 300,008 Caribbean, 1961 August (Box 10)
    Caneel Bay?
  - 300,009 Woodstock Mansion - Fallout Shelter?, 1962 February (Box 10)
    Installation of tanks or Fallout Shelter at Woodstock Mansion.
  - 300,010 Caribbean, 1962 March (Box 10)
  - 300,011 LSR and MFR Caribbean, 1962 April (Box 10)
    At Caneel Bay. Includes Allston Boyer, and others.
  - 300,012 LSR with unidentified woman and children, 1967 June (Box 10)
    One image.
  - 300,013 Caribbean, 1968 June (Box 10)
    One image. LSR, Allston Boyer, two women descending from row boat.
  - 300,013.1 Unidentified Hotel or Condo Building and Pool, 1969 January (Box 10)
    MFR on balcony?
  - 300,014 Caribbean, 1971 February - April (Box 10)
    3 images. LSR, Hitchcocks, and others. On boat, swimming.
  - 300,015 Stockholm and Hawaii, 1972 June (Box 10)
    LSR and MFR reviewing plans, possibly Hawaii; LSR and MFR sailing on the "Gloria," Stockholm, June 10, 1972.
  - 300,016 Unidentified lawn and stone walls, 1972 November (Box 10)
  - 300,016.1 Castro Wedding, 1972 December 22 (Box 10)
    Kim Castro, daughter of Nash and Bette Castro.
  - 300,017 Caribbean, 1973 (Box 10)
    LSR, MFR, and others.
  - 300,018 Unidentified, 1973 April (Box 10)
  - 300,019 Tennis, 1973 July (Box 10)
    One image of unidentified couple playing tennis.
  - 300,020 Caribbean, 1974 June (Box 10)
    LSR and others on boat.
  - 300,020.1 Central Park Statue, 1985 April (Box 10)
  - 300,021 MFR, 1976 September (Box 10)
  - 300,022 Caribbean and JY Ranch, 1976 November (Box 10)
    Includes LSR, MFR, DR.
  - 300,023 Girl in riding clothes and unidentified view, 1977 May (Box 10)
  - 300,024 LBJ Memorial Grove, 1977 October (Box 10)
    Two images
  - 300,025 LSR, Leonard Firestone, NAR, and others, 1978 October (Box 10)
    One image
  - 300,026 LSR and MFR by plane; Woodstock pool, 1979 May - September (Box 10)
  - 300,027 MFR, LSR, 1979 September (Box 10)
    With unidentified couple.
  - 300,028 Unidentified, 1979 September - October (Box 10)
    LSR with unidentified; Kay and Howard Somers.
  - 300,029 LSR with Nash and Bette Castro, 1980 October (Box 10)
    At Spruce Cottage, with unidentified man.
  - 300,030 Wyoming and Woodstock, circa 1980s (Box 10)
    LSR at JY Ranch with grandchildren; French family lunch, Woodstock gardens
  - 300,031 Pelicans and Parrots, 1978 February; 1981 December (Box 10)
    Color prints and slides.
  - 300,032 Japan, 1981 January (Box 10)
  - 300,033 Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 10)
    Beach, nature preserve?, Georgia, unidentified people,
  - 300,034 Billings Farm event, 1981 June (Box 10)
  - 300,035 Film Set in Pocantico, 1981 July (Box 10)
    Woody Allen's "A Midsummer Night's Sex Comedy" shot in Pocantico near Buttermilk Hill. House in background built for the shoot. Views of crew and set.
  - 300,036 Wayfarer Ketch Party, 1981 October 2 (Box 10)
    At Pocantico.
  - 300,037 Flowers, 1982 February (Box 10)
  - 300,038 Frederick Billings Statue Unveiling, 1982 July (Box 10)
    MFR and John French at unveiling ceremony.
  - 300,039 Painted portrait of MFR and Laura, 1983 October (Box 10)
  - 300,040 MFR, 1983 November (Box 10)
  - 300,041 JY Ranch and Hawaii, 1984 (Box 10)
    LSR and MFR fiftieth anniversary; JY Ranch, Appeal to the Great Spirit; views of Mauna Kea resort; flowers. Includes 2 disc negatives.
  - 300,042 Palm Beach, FL; Carolyn Lynch, Flowers, 1984 (Box 10)
    Disk negative only.
  - 300,043 Astors at St. Catherine's Island; Marion Weber Family, circa 1984 (Box 23)
    With LSR and MFR. Also, MFR serving tea at the Brick Church Fashion Show, 1981.
  - 300,044 MFR, 1984 March (Box 10)
    With flowers and balloons.
  - 300,045 LSR, MFR with Lady Bird Johnson, Town Lake, Austin, 1984 April 11 (Box 10)
    "The Land, the City and the Human Spirit" proclamation, Lou Neff Point on Town Lake, Austin. With Tom Wolfe and Mayor Ron Mullen.
  - 300,046 MFR, 1984 November (Box 10)
    With unidentified family
  - 300,047 Maine and Catskills, 1984 July (Box 10)
  - 300,048 Billings Farm and Museum; LSR and MFR with Guests, 834 Fifth Ave, 1984 November (Box 10)
    Unidentified guests; includes images of JDR 3 portrait.
  - 300,049 Litter of puppies, 1984 December (Box 10)